That channel applause!
These are our guests today!
Please! Here we go again!
I'm here! Sorry!
What? Isn't she too cute? That's enough!
Handshooter!
Alacoa!
This is Iyokura-san!
We've got two guys here who look like each other.
It's the first time I've been told we look alike.
The makeup.
Yes, the makeup.
I did their gal makeup.
Yes.
I did the same for Ana-chan.
Only her face was made to look like a gal.
Yes, sir.
I don't know how many times I'll bump into people today.
The visibility is so bad.
It's so black all the time, the upper half of my face.
But I heard the last Gal show was very well received.
I'm glad.
And they want to do a location shoot.
I understand.
But I have one concern.
When I hear how well it went.
I'm afraid I'm going to get all tangled up in it.
Oh...
Take care.
I'll do my best.
I understand.
Today's project.
Let's become a gal and enjoy Harajuku!
Today, we will try on new outfits today, guided by Ms. Nakagawa. I'm going to try on a new outfit. I'm going to try on a new outfit.
Let's try on some new clothes.
I will try on a new outfit.
Try on new clothes
Try on a new outfit
Wear your new clothes. What are you going to wear?
The clothes are just like normal Iwakura-san!
You look cute.
I'm in casual clothes, too.
Clothes?
It's normal.
You're both in casual clothes?
Yeah.
You're so cute.
But I don't think they're gals.
I'd like to dress you both like gals.
I'd like to dress you both like gals, so leave it to me.
We're going to Anap, where they sell gal clothes.
I've been doing this for a long time.
And they're all talking in gel.
I was going to say something really nice, but I wanted to say that it's really precious to be able to walk around in gal makeup, and that it's a real coming-of-age experience.
But I was really interested in their nails.
They're so cute!
Yes, with long nails!
I've been wanting to do some show race nails.
The show race is over, or rather, coming up soon.
I just finished two days ago.
Thank you very much.
I finished two days ago.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Not the grandchild of the loss, but the grandchild of the precious.
What's that supposed to mean?
Can you tell me what's going on?
You have three grandkids!
Yes, three grandchildren.
Even Sun Mei was surprised.
That's how I'd like to do it today.
I'm good.
Here's the store.
So cute!
I'm so excited!
I didn't know it was here.
Yes, it's right here in Harajuku, just off Takeshita-dori.
That's right!
There's a lot of gals here.
It's true, there are a lot of gals!
Hello!
Hello, hello.
Hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello.
Sparkle, sparkle, sparkle, sparkle, sparkle, sparkle, sparkle, sparkle...
Sparkle, sparkle, sparkle, sparkle, sparkle, sparkle, sparkle, sparkle.
You're so cute.
You're a gal.
You're a gal with a short waterfall.
It's more casual than you'd think.
That's right.
Sporty.
I think there's a lot going on with the times and all that, but...
This one has a lot of leopard print.
It's thick, isn't it?
It's cute, isn't it?
This would look good on Ami.
I think leopard print is a bit difficult to work with.
You don't wear leopard print or zebra print much?
I don't.
Then I'd like you to start running with animal prints.
I knew you and Papa Nekko-Nekko-Nekko-Nekko-Papa are here. I'm counting on you.
I've been wearing a lot of anups this winter.
I'm collaborating with the elf this winter.
I'm collaborating with Elf.
I'm collaborating with Anap.
Elf and Mr. Arakawa...
Arakawa is the one
Last time it was Gals
I produced and used their cosmetics.
And this time, I'm going to use your channel.
Thank you so much.
I'd love to, but I'm not a gal.
I wondered if I'd look good in it.
I'm a gal, so... No matter which one you wear.
I don't care which one you wear.
I'm so glad that Anochan complimented me on my grass.
I'm becoming a gal.
Agee.
Oh, Gal, you've become much more Gal.
I'm really happy.
I'm not lying, it's true, Anochan.
She's really cute.
I don't want you to think that all gals are like this.
The gal I have in my mind is just like this one, maybe too cute.
I can see some kind of pink.
Cute!
Isn't this it?
Yes, it is.
I'm wearing this pink sweatshirt.
And this is the pink hashtag Galmind.
I put it on.
This is the Galmind in zebra.
You mean you designed it?
With Mr. Anup.
Did you write the words?
Yes, we did.
Hashtags...
Like, a hashtag.
It's so cute!
What should I do?
I've decided.
I think it would be cute if the two of us wore different colors, but to be honest, I'm not sure which one would be better.
It's cute that you can see my belly.
Which do you prefer?
Um, the one you can't see.
The invisible one is better.
Then, I'll wear this one with my legs and pants out, like a winter gal, and long boots. So we'll be matching.
I see.
And, Mr. Seikura, please wear white.
And, after all, we are going to run out to the animals today, so...
This one.
This rabbit?
Rabbit knit.
Rabbit
Cute!
Matching bunnies.
Seriously?
Do you gals wear these?
Gals can wear whatever they want.
We're free.
This one? We're free to wear anything we want. Matching ones.
Matching ones.
I'm a sucker for matching. Are you okay with that?
I like matching, but I've never done it.
I'm glad we don't have that much.
Today's our anniversary, then?
Best friend's anniversary! I'm so happy!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. I love it.
I'm glad I was able to pull it off so naturally, better than having No-chan raise it up and say it to me.
Don't get me started on the male comedians!
What do you think? I feel like I've become a real gal.
It's like you've become a gal with a great mind!
When she's like this, she talks like a gal, too.
I didn't know she could talk like this.
They're perfect for each other.
You're really cute.
Thank you.
The girl in this dress talks like that.
Just now.
It's like she's talking out of her nose.
Don't say "like it's coming out of your nose.
It's embarrassing.
Don't say "mouth"!
Mr. Iwakura...
You should change your style.
This one is better.
You look great.
I'll be a gal starting tomorrow.
Welcome.
I'm sorry to bother you.
And you, Anochan.
We're all dressed alike.
Okay.
Hey, Ano!
Oh!
Oh, so cute!
Wow!
I thought I was being filmed on Takeshita-dori.
You threw it away, finally!
Anna-chan's gal part.
The roots.
What's the point of this?
Well, the fact that they're matching, and also because I've never seen them in pink before.
I want you to wear pink, and also because it's so flashy on its own.
Just by wearing it, you can see how different you look.
I wanted them to look different from their usual outfits.
It's cute and looks good on you.
Matching trousers
The pants are a different color, and the back has letters written by Anochan-san and Iwakura-san.
The back of the pants have English writing on a star, and their socks or arm warmers are also different colors.
I see... cute... the different colors give a different impression... cute... by the way... my nails are not done yet...
By the way, I don't think she has her nails done yet.
I don't think she has her nails done yet.
It's not my grandchildren's hands.
I'm not talking about my granddaughter's hands, but a gal's hands.
What? What's this?
I don't know.
She's putting nail polish on her granddaughter's hands.
I'm wearing a gal's hand.
You can use it as a walking stick if you like.
I was going to use it as a walking stick, but decided not to.
Can you hang it on your back?
No, I made it myself, so it's pretty fragile.
It just goes in?
It's just barely attached with double-sided tape.
I can't really hang it on the back.
I can't hang it on the back.
Well, then...
Excuse me.
How do you feel now that you're all gelled up?
I'm starting to sound like a gal.
You mentioned something else. What should I end it with? Gal...
Something like "kero".
Kero!
Kero is good.
Oh, really?
If you're so happy...
I didn't think I'd see you smile here.
I don't know...
I'm happy because I like Kero stuff.
I see.
Well then, now that we've all become gals
Let's go get a Puri to commemorate the occasion.
I'm going!
I'm looking forward to it!
KeroMichiBrother
Let's pick our favorite Puriki right away!
Let's pick one!
Did you take pictures when you were a student?
I took pictures sometimes when I was a student.
I also took pictures when I was an idol.
I don't take pictures these days.
Do you have any recommendations?
I can recommend some.
This one? It's close.
Yeah, it's close.
Moret, the goddess.
You mean you've taken pictures with this?
Yes, so let's do this one, Moret the Goddess! Moret, the goddess! You mean you've taken a picture of Moret the Goddess with this?
Yes!
Then let's do this one.
I was wondering when was the last time you took a picture with Arakawa.
We're good friends!
We take a lot of pictures.
At the end of Ariyoshi's wall or something.
Let's take this picture.
Elevator staff will pick something out for you Elevator staff will pick something out for you
Elevator staff will pick something out for you.
The elevator staff will pick something out for you.
Elevator staff pick something
Elevator staff picks and chooses
Elevator staff can pick something out for you.
Cal push or cal pushed
the elevator staff picks something
It's too much!
I love it.
He's so cute. - He's so cute.
Oh my God, what's that pose?
Heart!
What? Did you get it?
I just got it!
It's been like this the whole time.
Oh, it's so good! It's so good!
Who's that? It's Can! Oh, my God!
Do you want to do this? And the hearts.
I love it when you do the happy vertical.
That's for sure.
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
I'm done.
It's hard.
It's fun.
It didn't take long.
First shot
Select sticker
Start rakugaki
New feature
Sparkling eyes!
Really!
Here's a special item or
Something is good!
It's exactly what I want.
I like it.
Like, "We're the best!" or "We're the best!
Anything at all is fine.
What should I write? What shall I draw?
Please draw something nice and easy.
Draw it seriously.
What do you draw?
What are you drawing?
You have to do pretty colors.
Why?
Who wrote this?
It's not good.
It's fine.
It's fine, but we're free to doodle.
I don't need to fart.
Too cute! I love it! Too cute!
It's really cute!
Something's coming out!
It's coming out!
Oh, no!
Oh, my God!
It's coming out!
I'm so happy!
Butt!
Doodle butt.
Stop it.
Stop it. Stop it. Stop with the schoolyard doodles.
You told me I could write whatever I wanted. You told me to put my life on the line.
That sucks.
There's some loose poo.
He wrote "Agu" on it.
It's "Agu"!
Oh, no way.
Shoe brand? Yes, it's Boo Boo. I was interviewed a lot during the trip, so I felt a little relaxed.
You are just like Natalie.
What type is she?
I'd like to hear more about that in the next interview.
I want to eat something sweet.
Of course you do. Next, let's talk about crepes in Harajuku.
Crepe!
Crepe kelo!
Like, "I want to eat a crepe!
Eat kelo!
Eating kelo kelo
I always feel like I'm going to be something.
With you.